Del: Whatever’s inside these doors, those bugs don’t like it.
Del: There's nothing on this thing. How am I supposed to open it?
Luke: With the key.
Del: Why would the Emperor have a vault that can only be opened using the Force?
Luke: Why do you think?
Del: You're telling me the man who destroyed the Jedi Order is secretly one of them?
Luke: No. I'm telling you that as a boy on Coruscant you were frightened of the wrong thing.
Del: There's nothing dangerous in here. The Emperor is protecting junk.
Del: This is all worthless.
Luke: Not all of it.
Del: What is that?
Luke: I'd like to keep this compass, if you don't mind.
Del: My mission is to destroy this place. Why would I let you do that?
Luke: Because I asked.
Luke: Thank you.
Luke: I won’t stop you from destroying this vault. But wouldn’t you say the Empire has done enough damage to innocent worlds?
Luke: I'm glad we were brought together, Del.
Del: So, what happens now? We both walk off in separate directions and pretend like this never happened?
Luke: I don't think you can. There's still conflict in you.
Del: Of course there's conflict in me. I'm not blind. I know what the Empire's capable of. But what else is there?
Luke: A choice.
Del: The Rebellion?
Luke: No. A choice to be better.
Luke: May the Force be with you.